{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308190380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308190380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308190761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308190761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308191263","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308191262"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308191619","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308191617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308192036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308192035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308192528","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308192527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308192768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308192768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308195997","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308195997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308196030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308196030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308196743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308196743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308197137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308197137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308197431","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308197430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308197634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308197634"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308197826","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308197826"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308198140","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308198140"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308198363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308198362"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308201615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308201615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308202028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308202027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308204641","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308204640"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308204844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308204844"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308205051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308205051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308208555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308208554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308212288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308212288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308213318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308213317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308216058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308216057"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308216448","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308216447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308216948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308216948"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308217297","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308217296"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308217706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308217706"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308218185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308218184"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308218415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308218414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308221634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308221634"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308221687","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308221687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308222409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308222409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308222811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308222810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308223108","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308223108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308223318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308223317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308223515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308223515"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308223852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308223851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308224081","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308224080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308226727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308226726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308226823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308226823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 685d2c7d-3abb-49a4-a984-b75c4d0cc410"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308240651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308240651"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c4a6dab9-2d5a-45c2-95fa-10835ed3bacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-14-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308245283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308245283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c4a6dab9-2d5a-45c2-95fa-10835ed3bacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_10-3-12"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308251207","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308251207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c4a6dab9-2d5a-45c2-95fa-10835ed3bacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_10-3-12"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308256197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308256197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c4a6dab9-2d5a-45c2-95fa-10835ed3bacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_8-12-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308263892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308263892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c4a6dab9-2d5a-45c2-95fa-10835ed3bacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308279136","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308279136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c4a6dab9-2d5a-45c2-95fa-10835ed3bacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_12-14-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308285978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308285978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c4a6dab9-2d5a-45c2-95fa-10835ed3bacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308291332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308291331"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c4a6dab9-2d5a-45c2-95fa-10835ed3bacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_12-6-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308297363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308297363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c4a6dab9-2d5a-45c2-95fa-10835ed3bacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-11-6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308303718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308303718"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c4a6dab9-2d5a-45c2-95fa-10835ed3bacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-13-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308312245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308312245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c4a6dab9-2d5a-45c2-95fa-10835ed3bacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308318205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308318205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c4a6dab9-2d5a-45c2-95fa-10835ed3bacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308325287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308325286"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c4a6dab9-2d5a-45c2-95fa-10835ed3bacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308333633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308333633"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 963e83a8-dddb-435c-b78f-9d5ee5a09020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_CH-K-N"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308336471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308336471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 963e83a8-dddb-435c-b78f-9d5ee5a09020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_CH-Y-V"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308339533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308339533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 963e83a8-dddb-435c-b78f-9d5ee5a09020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_U-CH-L"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308342706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308342706"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 963e83a8-dddb-435c-b78f-9d5ee5a09020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_P-CH-R"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308345752","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308345752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 963e83a8-dddb-435c-b78f-9d5ee5a09020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_J-CH-O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308348709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308348709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 963e83a8-dddb-435c-b78f-9d5ee5a09020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_E-CH-A"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308351641","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308351641"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 963e83a8-dddb-435c-b78f-9d5ee5a09020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_CH-N-R"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308354599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308354599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 963e83a8-dddb-435c-b78f-9d5ee5a09020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_A-CH-W"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308357457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308357456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 963e83a8-dddb-435c-b78f-9d5ee5a09020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_CH-E-O"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308360450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308360450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 963e83a8-dddb-435c-b78f-9d5ee5a09020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_I-CH-P"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308366184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308366183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 963e83a8-dddb-435c-b78f-9d5ee5a09020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_I-CH-P"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308503560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308503559"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 963e83a8-dddb-435c-b78f-9d5ee5a09020"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_I-CH-P"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308503644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308503644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" ec6252c4-20ac-4191-8301-b9a41b049fef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308511354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308511353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" ec6252c4-20ac-4191-8301-b9a41b049fef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308518847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308518847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" ec6252c4-20ac-4191-8301-b9a41b049fef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308529317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308529317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308530359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308530358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308533006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308533006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308534040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308534040"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308536622","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308536622"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308536935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308536935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308537737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308537737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308540067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308540067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308542329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308542329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308542381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308542381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308543418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308543417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308545727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308545727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308548369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308548369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308548390","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308548390"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308563050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308563049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308563150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308563150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308570021","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308570021"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308581350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308581349"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308587535","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308587535"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" c1eb038a-debe-4ce2-925a-3140799c1879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308596991","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308596991"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 5e3a436b-11c6-438b-bc04-066f91409b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_E-CH-D"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308600808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308600808"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 5e3a436b-11c6-438b-bc04-066f91409b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-W-I"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308605577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308605577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 5e3a436b-11c6-438b-bc04-066f91409b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_U-D-P"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308610279","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308610279"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 5e3a436b-11c6-438b-bc04-066f91409b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-S-V"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308614802","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308614801"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 5e3a436b-11c6-438b-bc04-066f91409b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-H-K"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308618133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308618133"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 5e3a436b-11c6-438b-bc04-066f91409b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_Z-D-V"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308621460","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308621460"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 5e3a436b-11c6-438b-bc04-066f91409b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-Y-R"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308624446","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308624446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 5e3a436b-11c6-438b-bc04-066f91409b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-O-N"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308627836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308627836"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 5e3a436b-11c6-438b-bc04-066f91409b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_J-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308630795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308630795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 5e3a436b-11c6-438b-bc04-066f91409b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-U-G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308636533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308636532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 5e3a436b-11c6-438b-bc04-066f91409b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-U-G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308764930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308764929"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 5e3a436b-11c6-438b-bc04-066f91409b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-U-G"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308765007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308765007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 3850336c-659c-4b4d-aaad-f12b136cbed3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBACHO"," userResponse":" AMBACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308773143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308773143"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 58789dd8-3e4d-438a-9db5-842a8df15c4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_R-V-D"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308775989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308775989"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 58789dd8-3e4d-438a-9db5-842a8df15c4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-Z-L"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308778656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308778656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 58789dd8-3e4d-438a-9db5-842a8df15c4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-W-P"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308781512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308781512"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 58789dd8-3e4d-438a-9db5-842a8df15c4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-I-J"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308784636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308784636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 58789dd8-3e4d-438a-9db5-842a8df15c4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_B-D-G"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308787893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308787893"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 58789dd8-3e4d-438a-9db5-842a8df15c4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_P-D-W"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308791152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308791152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 58789dd8-3e4d-438a-9db5-842a8df15c4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_W-K-D"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308794205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308794205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 58789dd8-3e4d-438a-9db5-842a8df15c4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_CH-D-M"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308797094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308797093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 58789dd8-3e4d-438a-9db5-842a8df15c4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-T-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308800277","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308800277"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 58789dd8-3e4d-438a-9db5-842a8df15c4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_G-S-D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308806064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308806064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 58789dd8-3e4d-438a-9db5-842a8df15c4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_D_G-S-D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.decr.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308817109","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308817108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 58789dd8-3e4d-438a-9db5-842a8df15c4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_D_G-S-D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308824443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308824442"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 58789dd8-3e4d-438a-9db5-842a8df15c4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_D_G-S-D"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308834829","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308834829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0cdbe763-358b-47e0-97fe-4901de67112e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308835062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308835062"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0cdbe763-358b-47e0-97fe-4901de67112e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308836034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308836033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0cdbe763-358b-47e0-97fe-4901de67112e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308837311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308837310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0cdbe763-358b-47e0-97fe-4901de67112e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308840249","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308840249"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0cdbe763-358b-47e0-97fe-4901de67112e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308841121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308841120"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0cdbe763-358b-47e0-97fe-4901de67112e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308841437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308841436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0cdbe763-358b-47e0-97fe-4901de67112e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308842677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308842676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0cdbe763-358b-47e0-97fe-4901de67112e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308846197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308846197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0cdbe763-358b-47e0-97fe-4901de67112e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308847186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308847186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0cdbe763-358b-47e0-97fe-4901de67112e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308847451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308847451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0cdbe763-358b-47e0-97fe-4901de67112e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308848400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308848399"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0cdbe763-358b-47e0-97fe-4901de67112e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308851236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308851236"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0cdbe763-358b-47e0-97fe-4901de67112e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308852272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308852272"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0cdbe763-358b-47e0-97fe-4901de67112e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308852751","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308852750"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0cdbe763-358b-47e0-97fe-4901de67112e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308857296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308857296"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0cdbe763-358b-47e0-97fe-4901de67112e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308857386","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308857386"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0cdbe763-358b-47e0-97fe-4901de67112e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308866619","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308866619"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 9f3d895f-3fc6-4725-9854-9cf00ccc07c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308869680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308869680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 9f3d895f-3fc6-4725-9854-9cf00ccc07c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308875119","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308875118"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 9f3d895f-3fc6-4725-9854-9cf00ccc07c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308897478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308897477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 9f3d895f-3fc6-4725-9854-9cf00ccc07c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308911675","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308911675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 9f3d895f-3fc6-4725-9854-9cf00ccc07c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308919252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308919252"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 9f3d895f-3fc6-4725-9854-9cf00ccc07c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308926160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308926160"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 9f3d895f-3fc6-4725-9854-9cf00ccc07c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308950875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308950875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308955191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308955191"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308958818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308958818"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308962266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308962265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308966211","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308966211"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308969898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308969898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308973430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308973429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308977533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308977532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308981718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308981718"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308985691","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308985691"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308989225","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308989225"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308992524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308992524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548308995543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548308995543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309001680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309001680"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309007447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309007447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309010734","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309010734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309016684","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309016684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309022078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309022078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309038054","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309038054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309042360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309042359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309045740","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309045740"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309048821","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309048821"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309052561","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309052561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309056292","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309056292"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309062029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309062029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 80ee0908-6704-41f7-9fa6-6be375ca96cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309075728","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309075728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 1ffebd6b-932b-44a4-8a8b-7534981bdc7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-14-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309080496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309080496"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 1ffebd6b-932b-44a4-8a8b-7534981bdc7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309085541","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309085541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 1ffebd6b-932b-44a4-8a8b-7534981bdc7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309090841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309090841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 1ffebd6b-932b-44a4-8a8b-7534981bdc7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_12-14-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309099736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309099736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 1ffebd6b-932b-44a4-8a8b-7534981bdc7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_8-12-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309110174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309110174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 1ffebd6b-932b-44a4-8a8b-7534981bdc7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_12-6-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309127117","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309127116"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 1ffebd6b-932b-44a4-8a8b-7534981bdc7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-13-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309133206","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309133206"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 1ffebd6b-932b-44a4-8a8b-7534981bdc7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_10-3-12"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309138317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309138317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 1ffebd6b-932b-44a4-8a8b-7534981bdc7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_9-11-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309144540","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309144540"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 1ffebd6b-932b-44a4-8a8b-7534981bdc7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-11-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309151071","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309151071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 1ffebd6b-932b-44a4-8a8b-7534981bdc7e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.decr.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-11-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309162663","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309162663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 35a7873d-2901-4837-bd64-654646fa4c43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ENDESHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" ENDESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309166696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309166696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 35a7873d-2901-4837-bd64-654646fa4c43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ENDESHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309168250","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309168250"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 35a7873d-2901-4837-bd64-654646fa4c43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ELIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" ELIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309172846","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309172846"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 35a7873d-2901-4837-bd64-654646fa4c43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ELIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309174439","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309174438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 35a7873d-2901-4837-bd64-654646fa4c43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309178155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309178154"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 35a7873d-2901-4837-bd64-654646fa4c43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309180180","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309180180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 35a7873d-2901-4837-bd64-654646fa4c43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309180431","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309180430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 35a7873d-2901-4837-bd64-654646fa4c43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309192813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309192813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" d42bee1e-a790-455c-a212-b21ec330747d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ENDESHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" ENDESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309196848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309196848"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" d42bee1e-a790-455c-a212-b21ec330747d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ENDESHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309198398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309198398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" d42bee1e-a790-455c-a212-b21ec330747d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ELIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" ELIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309202712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309202712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" d42bee1e-a790-455c-a212-b21ec330747d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ELIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309204272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309204272"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" d42bee1e-a790-455c-a212-b21ec330747d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309207579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309207579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" d42bee1e-a790-455c-a212-b21ec330747d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309209587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309209587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" d42bee1e-a790-455c-a212-b21ec330747d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309209860","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309209860"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" d42bee1e-a790-455c-a212-b21ec330747d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309236855","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309236855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" bd6e6da3-ffbe-429a-986d-f133fbeb0946"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309240527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309240527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" bd6e6da3-ffbe-429a-986d-f133fbeb0946"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309267543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309267543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" bd6e6da3-ffbe-429a-986d-f133fbeb0946"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309287002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309287002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" bd6e6da3-ffbe-429a-986d-f133fbeb0946"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309309411","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309309411"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" bd6e6da3-ffbe-429a-986d-f133fbeb0946"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309328765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309328765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" bd6e6da3-ffbe-429a-986d-f133fbeb0946"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309351498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309351498"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" bd6e6da3-ffbe-429a-986d-f133fbeb0946"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_11"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309371040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309371039"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" bd6e6da3-ffbe-429a-986d-f133fbeb0946"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_13"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309392156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309392155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" bd6e6da3-ffbe-429a-986d-f133fbeb0946"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_13"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309392268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309392268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" bd6e6da3-ffbe-429a-986d-f133fbeb0946"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309404102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309404101"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" a54b3e2c-facb-4cff-9ec1-5401463a8beb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ENDESHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" ENDESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309407287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309407287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" a54b3e2c-facb-4cff-9ec1-5401463a8beb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ENDESHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" ENDESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309408918","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309408918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" a54b3e2c-facb-4cff-9ec1-5401463a8beb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ELIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" ELIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309411555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309411555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" a54b3e2c-facb-4cff-9ec1-5401463a8beb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ELIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" ELIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309413142","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309413141"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" a54b3e2c-facb-4cff-9ec1-5401463a8beb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309415553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309415553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" a54b3e2c-facb-4cff-9ec1-5401463a8beb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309417569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309417569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" a54b3e2c-facb-4cff-9ec1-5401463a8beb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309417672","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309417672"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" a54b3e2c-facb-4cff-9ec1-5401463a8beb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309428397","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309428397"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 6dca892d-6333-4a50-93a0-d8b114858975"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_9-10-15"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309437821","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309437821"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 6dca892d-6333-4a50-93a0-d8b114858975"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_1-4-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309450125","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309450124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 6dca892d-6333-4a50-93a0-d8b114858975"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_1-4-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309456208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309456208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 6dca892d-6333-4a50-93a0-d8b114858975"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_4-12-13"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309467548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309467548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 6dca892d-6333-4a50-93a0-d8b114858975"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_1-13-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309476227","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309476227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 6dca892d-6333-4a50-93a0-d8b114858975"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-13"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309484346","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309484346"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 6dca892d-6333-4a50-93a0-d8b114858975"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-13"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309493793","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309493793"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 6dca892d-6333-4a50-93a0-d8b114858975"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_0-1-10"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309502895","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309502895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 6dca892d-6333-4a50-93a0-d8b114858975"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-11-6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309508916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309508916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 6dca892d-6333-4a50-93a0-d8b114858975"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-13-6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309517120","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309517119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 6dca892d-6333-4a50-93a0-d8b114858975"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-13-6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309523663","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309523663"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 6dca892d-6333-4a50-93a0-d8b114858975"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309530223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309530223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 6dca892d-6333-4a50-93a0-d8b114858975"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309536953","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309536945"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 6dca892d-6333-4a50-93a0-d8b114858975"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_6_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309550635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309550635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309551009","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309551009"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309551491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309551491"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309551835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309551835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309552238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309552238"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309552712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309552712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309552935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309552935"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309556131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309556131"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309556173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309556172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309556890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309556890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309557283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309557283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309557588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309557587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309557797","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309557796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309557997","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309557997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309558347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309558347"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309558588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309558588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309561727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309561726"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309562139","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309562139"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309564720","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309564720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309564928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309564928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309565136","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309565135"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309568600","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309568600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309572367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309572364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309573394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309573394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309576090","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309576090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309576464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309576464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309576954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309576953"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309577300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309577300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309577710","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309577709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309578189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309578189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309578417","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309578417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309581626","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309581626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309581670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309581670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309582410","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309582409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309582811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309582811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309583105","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309583104"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309583324","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309583323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309583528","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309583528"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309583852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309583852"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309584076","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309584076"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309586678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309586676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309586773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309586773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309595216","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309595215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 18fbea1b-4bc6-4d91-8a5f-23f1120ce945"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309616951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309616951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8328926f-d49b-4910-8b5e-2c1285b45350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_H_CH"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309623635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309623634"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8328926f-d49b-4910-8b5e-2c1285b45350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_Y_B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309630334","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309630333"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8328926f-d49b-4910-8b5e-2c1285b45350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_E_G"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309636993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309636993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8328926f-d49b-4910-8b5e-2c1285b45350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_E_K"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309643669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309643669"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8328926f-d49b-4910-8b5e-2c1285b45350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_G_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309650340","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309650340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8328926f-d49b-4910-8b5e-2c1285b45350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_S_E"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309657031","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309657031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8328926f-d49b-4910-8b5e-2c1285b45350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_R_E"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309663678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309663678"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8328926f-d49b-4910-8b5e-2c1285b45350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_J_G_E"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309670417","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309670417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8328926f-d49b-4910-8b5e-2c1285b45350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_O_V"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309677135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309677135"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8328926f-d49b-4910-8b5e-2c1285b45350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_H_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309690446","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309690445"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8328926f-d49b-4910-8b5e-2c1285b45350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_L_H_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309703343","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309703343"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0a3cecdb-712b-48cb-a6c5-87e5206c4e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309709182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309709182"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0a3cecdb-712b-48cb-a6c5-87e5206c4e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_4-12-13"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309721549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309721549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0a3cecdb-712b-48cb-a6c5-87e5206c4e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_4-12-13"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309731394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309731394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0a3cecdb-712b-48cb-a6c5-87e5206c4e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309738180","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309738180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0a3cecdb-712b-48cb-a6c5-87e5206c4e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_9-10-15"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309744589","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309744589"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0a3cecdb-712b-48cb-a6c5-87e5206c4e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_1-4-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309751288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309751288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0a3cecdb-712b-48cb-a6c5-87e5206c4e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_1-13-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309757768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309757768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0a3cecdb-712b-48cb-a6c5-87e5206c4e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-13-6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309765807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309765807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0a3cecdb-712b-48cb-a6c5-87e5206c4e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-13"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309771469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309771469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0a3cecdb-712b-48cb-a6c5-87e5206c4e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-11-6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309800294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309800294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0a3cecdb-712b-48cb-a6c5-87e5206c4e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_0-1-10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309806937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309806936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0a3cecdb-712b-48cb-a6c5-87e5206c4e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL4.incr.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_10_0-1-10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309819563","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309819563"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309822275","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309822275"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309823828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309823828"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309826824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309826823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309828402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309828402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309831309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309831309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309832994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309832994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309835660","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309835659"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309837242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309837241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309840301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309840301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309841874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309841874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309844990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309844990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309846547","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309846547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309849301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309849301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309850872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309850872"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309853878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309853878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309855427","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309855427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309859173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309859172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309860735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309860735"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309863806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309863805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309865372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309865372"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309869156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309869156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309870712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309870712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309879399","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309879399"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309882937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309882937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309885970","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309885970"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309887438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309887438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309887515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309887515"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309909791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309909790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309910048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309910048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309918926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309918925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309929110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309929110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309936352","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309936351"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8674168d-ac81-42e5-a798-a5653fa1d084"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309947487","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309947487"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309950773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309950773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309960770","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309960770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309964312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309964312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309968843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309968843"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309972228","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309972227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309976224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309976224"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309979776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309979776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309983359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309983359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309986585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309986585"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309989943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309989943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309993575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309993575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548309997867","data":{"timestamp":" 1548309997867"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310001478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310001478"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310005578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310005577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310009438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310009438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310013329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310013329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310016422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310016422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310019868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310019868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310023244","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310023243"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310026572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310026571"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310029820","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310029820"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310032809","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310032809"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310035704","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310035704"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310039370","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310039370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310045279","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310045267"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10f1b34a-59bb-45b3-b229-6838910081fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310064204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310064204"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HI"," userResponse":" HI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310064479","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310064479"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310065284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310065283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310065389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310065389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310066240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310066239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310066685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310066684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310067712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310067711"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310068859","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310068859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310069217","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310069217"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310069806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310069806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310070696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310070696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYATIMA"," userResponse":" MAYATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310073922","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310073921"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" AGOSTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310074567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310074567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310075122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310075122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310075486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310075486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310076362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310076361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUGHULI"," userResponse":" SHUGHULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310077157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310077157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310077757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310077757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310078384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310078384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310079168","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310079168"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310079564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310079562"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310080389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310080389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310080915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310080915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310081791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310081791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310082649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310082649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310085890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310085889"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIYEFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310086600","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310086600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310087546","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310087546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310088284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310088283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" MKITE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310088948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310088948"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310089365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310089365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310089601","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310089600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310090050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310090050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKA"," userResponse":" MWAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310090783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310090783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310093460","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310093460"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310094494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310094494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEBEBWA"," userResponse":" AMEBEBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310095317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310095317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310095841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310095841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310096008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310096008"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310096603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310096603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310097361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310097361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310100614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310100614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310100900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310100899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310101875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310101875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310102551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310102551"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310104062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310104061"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" WALIMWONEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310105097","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310105097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" MKITE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310105435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310105434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" HURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310106419","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310106419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310109158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310109158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310110284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310110284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEKONDA"," userResponse":" AMEKONDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310110518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310110518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310110980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310110980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310111801","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310111801"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310114991","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310114990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310115443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310115443"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310116053","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310116053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310117002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310117001"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310117968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310117968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" MKITE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310118564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310118564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310119050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310119050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310119685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310119685"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFYA"," userResponse":" AFYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310122438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310122438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" ALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310123214","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310123214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310123477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310123477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310124172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310124172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310125051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310125051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310125886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310125885"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310126774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310126773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310129786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310129785"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310130491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310130490"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310131110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310131109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310131550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310131550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310131716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310131713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310132181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310132181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310132985","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310132985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" AGOSTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310134189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310134189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310134445","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310134445"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITUA"," userResponse":" ILITUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310135635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310135634"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310135700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310135700"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310136514","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310136514"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310139617","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310139617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310139891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310139891"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310140806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310140806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310141461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310141461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310143097","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310143097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" WALIHARAKISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310143625","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310143624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310144148","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310144147"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310146646","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310146646"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310146753","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310146753"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310147757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310147757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310148821","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310148821"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310149008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310149008"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310149587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310149587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310150564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310150564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUNGWA"," userResponse":" ALIFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310151281","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310151280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310151937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310151937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" BLANKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310152733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310152732"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310155557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310155557"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310156222","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310156222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIWA"," userResponse":" NDIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310157265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310157265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310157969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310157969"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310158904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310158904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" BLANKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310161623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310161623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310161829","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310161828"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310162414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310162414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310162580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310162580"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310163065","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310163065"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310163621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310163621"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310166329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310166329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310167195","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310167195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMLISHA"," userResponse":" ALIMLISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310167780","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310167780"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIWA"," userResponse":" NDIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310168526","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310168526"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310169102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310169102"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" CHUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310172170","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310172170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YATIMA"," userResponse":" YATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310172342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310172341"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310172937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310172937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310173791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310173791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310173946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310173946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310174950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310174950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310175514","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310175514"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALEA"," userResponse":" MALEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310178457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310178457"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKISHWA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKISHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310179188","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310179187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310188864","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310188864"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310189369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310189369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310190127","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310190127"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBEBWA"," userResponse":" KUBEBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310190645","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310190645"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310191272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310191272"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TREKTA"," userResponse":" TREKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310192087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310192087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310195145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310195141"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310195379","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310195378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310195973","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310195973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310196143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310196143"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310196764","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310196763"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIEZI"," userResponse":" MIEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310197364","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310197364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310200141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310200141"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Malea alikuwa kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALEA"," userResponse":" MALEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310201213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310201213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Malea alikuwa kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310203959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310203958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Malea alikuwa kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFARU"," userResponse":" KIFARU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310223679","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310223679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310224317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310224317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310224513","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310224513"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310225208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310225208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310225504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310225504"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310226249","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310226249"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENKARE"," userResponse":" ENKARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310227536","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310227535"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYE"," userResponse":" AMBAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310228132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310228132"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310228727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310228727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYATI"," userResponse":" NYATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310229476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310229476"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310231969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310231968"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda pamoja kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310232782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310232782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda pamoja kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310233564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310233564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda pamoja kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310234299","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310234299"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda pamoja kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310238053","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310238053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310238818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310238818"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310240062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310240061"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310240527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310240527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310241533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310241533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMSHWA"," userResponse":" ALIAMSHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310242072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310242071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310242722","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310242722"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310243086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310243086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310243718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310243718"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBIA"," userResponse":" AMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310246819","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310246819"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBIA"," userResponse":" AMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310247555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310247554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310247803","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310247803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310248349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310248349"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310248554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310248554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310249168","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310249168"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIEZI"," userResponse":" MIEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310249865","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310249865"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITANO"," userResponse":" MITANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310252505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310252505"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHISI"," userResponse":" ALIHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310253172","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310253172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310253504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310253504"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310254501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310254501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHOVU"," userResponse":" UCHOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310255350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310255350"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310255673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310255673"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310256210","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310256209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310257215","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310257214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310259549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310259549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310260155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310260155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310260361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310260361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310260936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310260936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGO"," userResponse":" SHINGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310261384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310261383"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310261814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310261813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REFU"," userResponse":" REFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310262954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310262954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310264160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310264159"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIISHIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310264747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310264747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" CHUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310265236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310265224"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310265998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310265998"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310266783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310266782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMLISHA"," userResponse":" KUMLISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310269854","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310269854"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPACHA"," userResponse":" MAPACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310270480","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310270480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABEI"," userResponse":" ABEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310270706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310270705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310271401","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310271401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOIT"," userResponse":" MOIT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310272506","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310272506"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310273653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310273653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310273719","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310273719"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310274305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310274305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310275102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310275102"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" AGOSTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310277791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310277791"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310278795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310278795"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEZALIWA"," userResponse":" WAMEZALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310279301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310279301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310279565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310279565"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHACHE"," userResponse":" CHACHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310279856","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310279856"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310282616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310282615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wagonjwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310283780","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310283780"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wagonjwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAGONJWA"," userResponse":" WAGONJWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310284345","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310284345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wagonjwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310287304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310287304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310287980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310287979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310289644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310289643"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" ALIHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310290749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310290749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310291545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310291545"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABEI"," userResponse":" ABEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310292509","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310292509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAGA"," userResponse":" ALIAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310293205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310293205"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIA"," userResponse":" DUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310293971","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310293971"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIKI"," userResponse":" WIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310294577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310294576"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310295272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310295272"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310295517","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310295517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310296154","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310296154"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310296632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310296632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310297629","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310297629"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310300294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310300294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310300981","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310300981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310301187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310301187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310302085","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310302085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310302700","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310302700"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310304217","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310304217"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWOKOA"," userResponse":" WALIMWOKOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310304860","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310304860"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOIT"," userResponse":" MOIT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310317067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310317067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYATIMA"," userResponse":" MAYATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310317322","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310317322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310317847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310317847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" MWISHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310318571","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310318571"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310319028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310319028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310319181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310319181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310319729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310319728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310320657","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310320657"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" AGOSTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310321607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310321607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310322444","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310322444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOPI"," userResponse":" KOPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310323501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310323500"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KEPI"," userResponse":" KEPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310324138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310324138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310324884","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310324883"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KEJI"," userResponse":" KEJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310327641","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310327641"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310328606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310328606"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANASIMBA"," userResponse":" WANASIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310329505","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310329505"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310329753","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310329752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310330305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310330305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310330529","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310330529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310330961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310330961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIKI"," userResponse":" WIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310331416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310331416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310334075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310334074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihisi kiu sana walikpofika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHISI"," userResponse":" WALIHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310334493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310334492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihisi kiu sana walikpofika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIU"," userResponse":" KIU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310335090","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310335090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihisi kiu sana walikpofika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310336186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310336186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihisi kiu sana walikpofika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKPOFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIKPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310339578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310339578"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310339993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310339993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310340799","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310340799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310341363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310341363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310342677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310342677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWAPENDA"," userResponse":" WALIWAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310343281","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310343281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310343780","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310343779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310344567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310344566"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310344968","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310344967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310345861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310345861"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATUKUTU"," userResponse":" WATUKUTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310348853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310348853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtukutu zaidi alikuwa Lobolia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTUKUTU"," userResponse":" MTUKUTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310349418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310349418"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtukutu zaidi alikuwa Lobolia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310350024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310350024"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtukutu zaidi alikuwa Lobolia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310350559","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310350559"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtukutu zaidi alikuwa Lobolia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LOBOLIA"," userResponse":" LOBOLIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310353394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310353394"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LOBOLIA"," userResponse":" LOBOLIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310354291","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310354291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" ALIZOEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310355036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310355036"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFICHA"," userResponse":" KUFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310355832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310355832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWANI"," userResponse":" MIWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310355896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310355896"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310356580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310356580"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310359676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310359676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310360274","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310360274"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310360928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310360928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310361786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310361785"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310362874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310362874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAFANYA"," userResponse":" WANAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310363630","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310363630"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDII"," userResponse":" BIDII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310367823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310367822"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWATUNZA"," userResponse":" KUWATUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310373023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310373023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310373581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310373581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310374287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310374287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310385463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310385463"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANATUMAI"," userResponse":" WANATUMAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310385768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310385768"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310386207","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310386207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310386779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310386779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310387935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310387934"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYATIMA"," userResponse":" MAYATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310388467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310388467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310389596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310389596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATAWEZA"," userResponse":" WATAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310390880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310390880"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJITEGEMEA"," userResponse":" KUJITEGEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310391867","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310391867"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYEWE"," userResponse":" WENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310392319","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310392319"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310392779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310392778"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310395447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310395446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu wataweza kurudi porini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310396578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310396578"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu wataweza kurudi porini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATAWEZA"," userResponse":" WATAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310397175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310397174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu wataweza kurudi porini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310397999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310397999"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu wataweza kurudi porini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PORINI"," userResponse":" PORINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310400707","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310400706"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310401270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310401269"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310401984","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310401984"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310402318","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310402318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310402553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310402552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310403556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310403556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGAPI"," userResponse":" WANGAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310406021","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310406021"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOMA"," userResponse":" SOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310406606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310406606"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310407534","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310407534"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310408342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310408342"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310408928","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310408928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UJIBU"," userResponse":" UJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310409603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310409602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" MASWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310409897","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310409897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310455277","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310455277"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310455412","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310455412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 05c51020-7f55-4f28-bdc5-47628f2e2c14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310472079","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310472079"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HI"," userResponse":" HI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310472353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310472353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310473158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310473158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310473262","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310473262"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310474110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310474110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310474557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310474557"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310475582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310475581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310476728","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310476728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310477090","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310477090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310477675","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310477675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310478557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310478557"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYATIMA"," userResponse":" MAYATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310481780","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310481780"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" AGOSTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310482425","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310482425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310482990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310482990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310483355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310483355"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310484248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310484248"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUGHULI"," userResponse":" SHUGHULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310485045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310485045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310485620","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310485620"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310494598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310494598"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310495382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310495382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310495777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310495776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310496606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310496606"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310497138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310497138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310498014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310498013"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310498872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310498871"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Agosti ulikuwa mwezi wenye shughuli nyingi sana kwa Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310501848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310501848"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEFIKA"," userResponse":" ALIYEFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310502565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310502565"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310503522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310503522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310504242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310504242"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" MKITE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310504907","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310504906"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310505322","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310505322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310505549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310505549"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310505994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310505994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKA"," userResponse":" MWAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310506711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310506710"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyefika kwanza alikuwa Mkite wa umri wa mwaka mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310509379","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310509378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310510424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310510424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEBEBWA"," userResponse":" AMEBEBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310511245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310511244"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310511773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310511773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310511954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310511953"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310512558","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310512558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310513313","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310513313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amebebwa katika lori la kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310516514","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310516514"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310516798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310516798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310517743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310517743"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310518416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310518416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310519911","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310519911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWONEA"," userResponse":" WALIMWONEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310520947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310520947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" MKITE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310521271","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310521271"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HURUMA"," userResponse":" HURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310522240","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310522240"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwonea Mkite huruma sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310525036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310525036"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310526159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310526159"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEKONDA"," userResponse":" AMEKONDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310526492","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310526491"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310526946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310526946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310527751","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310527751"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa amekonda na mwenye huzuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUZUNI"," userResponse":" HUZUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310530852","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310530852"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310531276","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310531276"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310531869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310531869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310532802","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310532802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310533757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310533757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKITE"," userResponse":" MKITE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310534353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310534353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310534839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310534839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310535475","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310535475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini muda mfupi baadaye Mkite alikuwa mwenye afya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFYA"," userResponse":" AFYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310538300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310538300"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" ALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310539067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310539066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310539310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310539310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310540006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310540006"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310540872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310540872"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310541698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310541698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310542585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310542583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kucheza na wanyama wengine katika chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310545690","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310545690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310546441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310546441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310547061","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310547061"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310547494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310547494"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310547652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310547652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310548123","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310548122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310548936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310548936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" AGOSTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310550147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310550147"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310550406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310550406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITUA"," userResponse":" ILITUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310551601","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310551601"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310551670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310551670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310552487","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310552487"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku nyingine katika mwezi huo wa Agosti helikopta ilitua mbele ya chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310555556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310555555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310555845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310555845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310556781","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310556781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310557428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310557428"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310559064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310559064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHARAKISHA"," userResponse":" WALIHARAKISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310559600","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310559600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310560116","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310560116"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliharakisha kwenda nje."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310562595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310562595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310562698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310562698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310563726","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310563725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310564783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310564782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310564960","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310564960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310565570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310565570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOVU"," userResponse":" NDOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310566548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310566548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFUNGWA"," userResponse":" ALIFUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310567265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310567265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310567923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310567923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" BLANKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310568736","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310568736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndani ya helikopta mtoto wa ndovu alifungwa katika blanketi kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310571555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310571554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310572220","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310572220"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIWA"," userResponse":" NDIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310573268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310573268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310573998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310573998"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310582403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310582402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni Ndiwa aliyekuwa katika blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" BLANKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310584998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310584997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310585214","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310585214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310585798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310585798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310585979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310585979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310586464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310586464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310587025","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310587025"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa siku tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310589740","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310589740"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310590606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310590606"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMLISHA"," userResponse":" ALIMLISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310591199","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310591199"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIWA"," userResponse":" NDIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310591963","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310591963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310592553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310592553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi alimlisha Ndiwa kutumia chupa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" CHUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310595667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310595667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YATIMA"," userResponse":" YATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310595833","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310595833"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310596418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310596418"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310597273","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310597273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310597427","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310597427"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310598447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310598447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310599012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310599012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yatima wa tatu mwezi huo alikuwa Malea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALEA"," userResponse":" MALEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310601944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310601944"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKISHWA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKISHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310602651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310602650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310603624","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310603624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310604158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310604158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310604913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310604913"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBEBWA"," userResponse":" KUBEBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310605447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310605447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310606072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310606072"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TREKTA"," userResponse":" TREKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310606887","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310606887"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikishwa katika chekechea kwa kubebwa kwenye trekta nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310609472","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310609472"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310609706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310609706"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310610301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310610301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310610475","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310610474"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310611098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310611098"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIEZI"," userResponse":" MIEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310611692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310611691"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na umri wa miezi sita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310614471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310614471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Malea alikuwa kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MALEA"," userResponse":" MALEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310615552","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310615552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Malea alikuwa kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310616303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310616303"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Malea alikuwa kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFARU"," userResponse":" KIFARU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310618982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310618982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310619597","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310619597"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310619797","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310619797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310620492","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310620492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310620784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310620784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310621573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310621572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENKARE"," userResponse":" ENKARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310622873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310622873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYE"," userResponse":" AMBAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310623470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310623466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310624084","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310624084"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYATI"," userResponse":" NYATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310624839","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310624839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa rafiki wa karibu wa Enkare ambaye alikuwa nyati mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310627442","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310627441"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda pamoja kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310628267","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310628267"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda pamoja kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310629044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310629043"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda pamoja kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310629786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310629786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walienda pamoja kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310632811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310632811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310633579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310633579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310634838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310634838"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310635294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310635294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310636298","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310636298"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAMSHWA"," userResponse":" ALIAMSHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310636838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310636838"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310637473","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310637473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310637841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310637841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310638466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310638466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja kila mmoja aliamshwa na kufika kwa Ambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBIA"," userResponse":" AMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310641567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310641567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBIA"," userResponse":" AMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310642301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310642301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310642537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310642537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310643070","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310643069"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310643264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310643264"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310643878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310643878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIEZI"," userResponse":" MIEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310644572","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310644572"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia alikuwa na umri wa miezi mitano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITANO"," userResponse":" MITANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310647247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310647247"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHISI"," userResponse":" ALIHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310647913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310647912"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310648239","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310648239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310649235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310649235"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UCHOVU"," userResponse":" UCHOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310650050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310650050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310650287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310650287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310650813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310650813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" SAFARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310651807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310651807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alihisi njaa na uchovu baada ya safari ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310654444","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310654444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310655049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310655049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310655225","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310655225"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310655782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310655782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGO"," userResponse":" SHINGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310656232","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310656231"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310656648","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310656648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REFU"," userResponse":" REFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310657755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310657755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310658971","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310658970"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIISHIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310659557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310659556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" CHUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310660027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310660027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310660772","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310660772"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310661561","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310661561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ya shingo lake refu Mlinzi aliishikia chupa juu ili kumlisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMLISHA"," userResponse":" KUMLISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310664716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310664716"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPACHA"," userResponse":" MAPACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310665364","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310665364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABEI"," userResponse":" ABEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310665589","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310665589"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310666287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310666287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOIT"," userResponse":" MOIT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310667391","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310667391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310668540","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310668539"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310668603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310668603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310669189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310669189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310669994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310669994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapacha Abei na Moit walifika katikati ya mwezi Agosti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" AGOSTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310672665","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310672665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310673675","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310673675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEZALIWA"," userResponse":" WAMEZALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310674179","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310674179"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310674443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310674443"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHACHE"," userResponse":" CHACHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310674727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310674727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310677501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310677501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wagonjwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310678666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310678666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wagonjwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAGONJWA"," userResponse":" WAGONJWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310679232","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310679232"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wagonjwa sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310682174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310682174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310682843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310682843"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310684498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310684498"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" ALIHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310685603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310685603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310686398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310686398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABEI"," userResponse":" ABEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310687363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310687363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIAGA"," userResponse":" ALIAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310688058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310688058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIA"," userResponse":" DUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310688823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310688823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIKI"," userResponse":" WIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310689428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310689428"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310690122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310690122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310690367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310690367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310691008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310691007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310691491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310691491"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310692488","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310692487"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alihuzunika wakati Abei aliaga dunia wiki moja baada ya kufika pale chekechea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310695160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310695160"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310695844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310695843"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310696048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310696047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310696941","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310696941"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310697563","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310697563"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310699077","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310699077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIMWOKOA"," userResponse":" WALIMWOKOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310699744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310699744"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake walimwokoa Moit."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOIT"," userResponse":" MOIT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310703079","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310703079"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYATIMA"," userResponse":" MAYATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310703319","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310703319"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310703862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310703862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" MWISHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310704577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310704577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310705044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310705044"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310705203","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310705203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310705727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310705727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310706655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310706655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AGOSTI"," userResponse":" AGOSTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310707582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310707582"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310708460","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310708460"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOPI"," userResponse":" KOPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310709518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310709518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KEPI"," userResponse":" KEPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310710174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310710174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310710920","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310710920"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mayatima wa mwisho kufika mwezi huo wa Agosti walikuwa Kopi Kepi na Keji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KEJI"," userResponse":" KEJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310713519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310713519"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310714464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310714464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANASIMBA"," userResponse":" WANASIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310715359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310715359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310715594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310715594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310716124","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310716123"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310716348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310716348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310716771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310716771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIKI"," userResponse":" WIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310717227","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310717227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawa wanasimba walikuwa na umri wa wiki mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310719935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310719934"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihisi kiu sana walikpofika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHISI"," userResponse":" WALIHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310720352","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310720352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihisi kiu sana walikpofika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIU"," userResponse":" KIU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310720965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310720964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihisi kiu sana walikpofika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310722067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310722067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walihisi kiu sana walikpofika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKPOFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIKPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310725402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310725402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310725823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310725823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310726644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310726643"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASAIDIZI"," userResponse":" WASAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310727212","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310727212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310728516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310728516"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWAPENDA"," userResponse":" WALIWAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310729122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310729121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310729609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310729609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310730437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310730437"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310730813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310730813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310731717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310731717"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlinzi na wasaidizi wake waliwapenda wanyama wote hata wale watukutu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATUKUTU"," userResponse":" WATUKUTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310734659","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310734659"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtukutu zaidi alikuwa Lobolia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTUKUTU"," userResponse":" MTUKUTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310735224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310735224"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtukutu zaidi alikuwa Lobolia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310735828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310735828"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtukutu zaidi alikuwa Lobolia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310736371","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310736371"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtukutu zaidi alikuwa Lobolia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LOBOLIA"," userResponse":" LOBOLIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310739177","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310739177"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LOBOLIA"," userResponse":" LOBOLIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310740072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310740072"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" ALIZOEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310740836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310740836"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFICHA"," userResponse":" KUFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310741632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310741632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWANI"," userResponse":" MIWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310741696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310741696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310742362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310742362"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lobolia alizoea kuficha miwani ya Mlinzi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLINZI"," userResponse":" MLINZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310745424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310745424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310746020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310746020"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310746674","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310746674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310747519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310747519"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310748604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310748603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAFANYA"," userResponse":" WANAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310749366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310749365"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDII"," userResponse":" BIDII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310750478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310750478"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWATUNZA"," userResponse":" KUWATUNZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310751157","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310751157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310751718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310751718"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310752445","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310752445"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wote hapo chekechea wanafanya bidii kuwatunza wanyama hawa watoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310755332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310755332"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANATUMAI"," userResponse":" WANATUMAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310755641","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310755641"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310756075","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310756075"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310756641","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310756641"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310757798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310757798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYATIMA"," userResponse":" MAYATIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310758311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310758311"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310759446","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310759446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATAWEZA"," userResponse":" WATAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310760730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310760730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJITEGEMEA"," userResponse":" KUJITEGEMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310761720","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310761720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYEWE"," userResponse":" WENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310762156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310762156"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310762602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310762602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanatumai kwamba siku moja mayatima hao wataweza kujitegemea wenyewe siku moja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310765203","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310765203"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu wataweza kurudi porini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310766329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310766329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu wataweza kurudi porini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATAWEZA"," userResponse":" WATAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310766922","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310766922"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu wataweza kurudi porini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310767747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310767746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu wataweza kurudi porini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PORINI"," userResponse":" PORINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310770460","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310770460"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310771023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310771023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310771742","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310771741"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310772078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310772078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310772314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310772313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310773320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310773320"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wana umri gani na ni wangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGAPI"," userResponse":" WANGAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310775782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310775782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOMA"," userResponse":" SOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310776367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310776366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310777292","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310777292"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADITHI"," userResponse":" HADITHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310778098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310778098"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310778683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310778683"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UJIBU"," userResponse":" UJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310779357","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310779357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" MASWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310779652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310779652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310796313","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310796313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0db61abd-e8aa-4dbb-876a-4da188510dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Soma tena hadithi kisha ujibu maswali haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310813772","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310813772"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0b585944-f67a-4e9e-80f5-e3747d43c0e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310818100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310818100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0b585944-f67a-4e9e-80f5-e3747d43c0e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310819667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310819667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0b585944-f67a-4e9e-80f5-e3747d43c0e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FAGIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310823927","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310823927"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0b585944-f67a-4e9e-80f5-e3747d43c0e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FAGIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310825506","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310825506"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0b585944-f67a-4e9e-80f5-e3747d43c0e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FULANA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANA"," userResponse":" FULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310828059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310828059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0b585944-f67a-4e9e-80f5-e3747d43c0e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FULANA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANA"," userResponse":" FULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310831632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310831632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0b585944-f67a-4e9e-80f5-e3747d43c0e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FARASI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" FARASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310835557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310835556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0b585944-f67a-4e9e-80f5-e3747d43c0e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FARASI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310837147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310837147"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0b585944-f67a-4e9e-80f5-e3747d43c0e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310841582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310841581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0b585944-f67a-4e9e-80f5-e3747d43c0e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310843614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310843613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0b585944-f67a-4e9e-80f5-e3747d43c0e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" FISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310843980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310843980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 0b585944-f67a-4e9e-80f5-e3747d43c0e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310857097","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310857097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10bec420-c02f-4245-8d66-54b36944955f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310861084","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310861084"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10bec420-c02f-4245-8d66-54b36944955f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310862675","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310862675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10bec420-c02f-4245-8d66-54b36944955f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FAGIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310866507","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310866507"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10bec420-c02f-4245-8d66-54b36944955f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FAGIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310868105","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310868105"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10bec420-c02f-4245-8d66-54b36944955f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FUPI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310871625","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310871625"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10bec420-c02f-4245-8d66-54b36944955f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FUPI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310873223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310873223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10bec420-c02f-4245-8d66-54b36944955f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FULANA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANA"," userResponse":" FULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310877047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310877047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10bec420-c02f-4245-8d66-54b36944955f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FULANA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310878649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310878649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10bec420-c02f-4245-8d66-54b36944955f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FARASI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" FARASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310882382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310882382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10bec420-c02f-4245-8d66-54b36944955f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FARASI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310883963","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310883963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10bec420-c02f-4245-8d66-54b36944955f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310888215","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310888215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10bec420-c02f-4245-8d66-54b36944955f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-F.rand.21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310890231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310890230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10bec420-c02f-4245-8d66-54b36944955f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" FISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310890501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310890501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 10bec420-c02f-4245-8d66-54b36944955f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-F.rand.21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" FISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310904453","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310904452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8fd36a5e-1849-4e7f-9f7e-6f39a15504ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_10-5-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310910255","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310910255"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8fd36a5e-1849-4e7f-9f7e-6f39a15504ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-1-10"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310916032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310916032"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8fd36a5e-1849-4e7f-9f7e-6f39a15504ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-0-11"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310922493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310922492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8fd36a5e-1849-4e7f-9f7e-6f39a15504ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-10-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310929183","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310929183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8fd36a5e-1849-4e7f-9f7e-6f39a15504ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_2-11-13"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310944415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310944415"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8fd36a5e-1849-4e7f-9f7e-6f39a15504ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_2-11-13"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310951335","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310951335"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8fd36a5e-1849-4e7f-9f7e-6f39a15504ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-11-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548310971950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548310971950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_083615"," gameId":" 8fd36a5e-1849-4e7f-9f7e-6f39a15504ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-11-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}